{
    "id": "08ddc2253ecd4fd29df884f56e3e0ff9",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ............................... go to bed at 10 o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "once",
                "ever",
                "usually"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "52b0573bc45f497a8813ed7bf7ebb817"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have …………………. been to the USA.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never",
                "ever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a966550f3d5a4bf0a1018ca0857c2ec5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been to Australia just …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "one",
                "once",
                "ones"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e414678e51484504896d0339e6e27186"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. take a bath before I go to bed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "once",
                "always",
                "ever"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e5b2f223a5b4642aa34ec8d2f3c8c72"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandparents live in Kerala. I visit them .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "once",
                "often"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9eb1b20ca594f53b44df6c6fa793466"
        },
        {
            "question": "My friends are ............................................. non-smokers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "mostly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be676a84707b45308b8345381c070ef7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ....................................... impressed with her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "such",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3e18bf5eeed54dbcad519aabbc4aa967"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................................... go for a walk in the park.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "some time",
                "sometime",
                "sometimes"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7f14bc538ee04bb7b45bdebd1bcf8d49"
        },
        {
            "question": "I watch English films ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "once",
                "always",
                "occasionally"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7a00c21083dd48f6ab850e5a1112e550"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ...................................... go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rare",
                "once",
                "rarely"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e25d2e97e520478d8518cd73db386d24"
        }
    ]
}